Nguyen Tuong Duy



64 Binh Quoi Street Binh Thanh District Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

E-mail: duy.pateo@gmail.com

Website: http://duypateo.github.io

Phone: (+84) 165 4265 303

SUMMARY

I'm Duy and I'm a Developer. I have experience with Web developement technologies. Programing language is only the tools and the most important thing is programing logic thinking and problem solving skills that I want to improve in my career opportunities.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FHH STARTUP

Front End Developer

Description:

- Building Customer website
- Building Landing page builder web application

Technologies:

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Jquery
- Python Flask
- Jinja template
- GIT (Bitbucket)
- Foundation Framework
- Boostrap Framework

phatwifi4g.com

Web Developer - Freelancer

Description:

- Building Ecommerce Website
- Both Frontend and Backend development
- Maintain and Support

Technologies:

- Pure PHP
- MySQL Database
- HTML/CSS/JS

January 2017 - December 2017

September 2017 - October 2017

Tìm Việc Nhanh

January 2018 - January 2018

HTML, CSS Freelancer

Description:

■ Code HTML CSS from PSD template

Technologies:

- HTML
- CSS

phithienky.com February 2018 - May 2018

Web Developer

Description:

- Building Online Novel Reading Website
- Both Frontend and Backend development

Technologies:

- PHP Laravel Framework
- MySQL Database
- HTML/CSS/JS

OPPO Vietnam March 2018 - July 2018

Backend Developer

Description:

- Develope ERP System with Team
- Create websites for Marketing Campaign
- Research and build mobile application from Website technologies.

Technologies:

- PHP
- Zend PHP Framework
- Phalcon PHP Framework
- Apache Cordova

EDUCATION

Information Technology

Ho Chi Minh University of Transport

Skills:

- C++
- C#
- Java
- Mobile Programing
- HTML/CSS/JS
- PHP

INTERESTS

Listen to Music

September 2014 - July 2018

Nguyen Tuong Duy

- Watching Movies
- Reading
- Photography
- Travel
- Running

LANGUAGE

- Vietnamese (Native)
- English (Basic Comunication, Read Document, Write)

Nguyen Tuong Duy 3